#### Contact

239.216.7083 (Mobile)

www.linkedin.com/in/jimmydascani (LinkedIn) Arthrex.com (Company)

### Top Skills

Team Leadership
Public Relations
Employee Engagement

### Languages

English

#### Honors-Awards

# 1 Nursing Engagement Scores in the Country for 2013 - 2014 Director of the Year

# Jimmy Dascani

Arthrex/Former Hospital CEO and CNO

Naples, Florida

# Summary

Enthusiastic Gen-X health care leader with a passion for advancing care and elevating the patient, staff and physician experience. As a former hospital CEO and CNO, I am now leading an important value initiative for Arthrex to build meaningful partnerships with organizations around the world.

Contact me to discuss upcoming educational opportunities for health care professionals.

## Experience

#### Arthrex

Health Care Executive/Administrator Relations May 2017 - Present (3 years 3 months)

Global Headquarters: Naples, Florida Area

Proud to be part of a company that manufactures, sterilizes and quality controls products in AMERICA!

Leading a new strategic division at Arthrex, Inc. - the global leader in medical education and orthopedic innovation. As Director of Health Care Administrator Relations, my focus is to educate health care professionals about the multitude of ways Arthrex can be an incredibly strong strategic partner in advancing care while improving he patient and clinician experiences.

#### Confidential

Physician Staffing and Hospital Consulting Company Owner January 2013 - July 2017 (4 years 7 months)

Sold

Landmark Hospitals Chief Executive Officer April 2015 - April 2017 (2 years 1 month)

Naples, Florida Area

# Martin Memorial Healthcare System/HealthSouth Interim CEO/CNO

February 2013 - March 2015 (2 years 2 months)

Stuart, Florida

Health Management Associates, Inc.
System Critical Care Director
October 2008 - February 2013 (4 years 5 months)

Naples, Florida Area

Millennium Financial Group / Collegiate Financial Services Chief Financial Officer / Partner October 2001 - October 2008 (7 years 1 month) Pittsburgh, PA

## U.S. Department of Veterans Affairs

Registered Nurse

June 1995 - October 2001 (6 years 5 months)

Pittsburgh, PA

Registered nurse on various specialty units - Liver Transplant, Stepdown, Cardiac Intensive Care Unit, Medical Intensive Care Unit, Surgical Intensive Care Unit

United States Coast Guard
USCG Reservist
January 1990 - January 1995 (5 years 1 month)
Ohio and Pennsylvania

## Education

Duquesne University
Bachelor's Degree, BSN · (1991 - 1995)

#### N/A

Financial/Registered Securities License, Banking, Corporate, Finance, and Securities Law (2001 - 2007)

#### N/A

Licensed in PA and Florida, Mortgage Banking (2001 - 2007)